漫威影业
谢谢您  斯坦
本字幕由网络爱好者联盟原创翻译
欢迎加入我们 www.ZiMuZu.pub
在保留译者名单的前提下任何人不需要经得我们的同意
可用本字幕做任何用途因此所产生的后果由您自行承担
■
翻译：  陆修    2円    summer_j2000    朱麒蓉
翻译： 爱妮妮的Xnnnner      扒虾爬子大师    oops黑吃黑    我要头发不要校对
■
翻译：  爱惊队的HI.T    爱寇森的Sam    爱佩佩的马丁    爱基神的奶茶
校对： 想吸噬元兽的刺罗森林
■
后期： LD    Charles zhang
总监： LD
■
哈
拉
星
克
里
文
明
母
星
您知道现在几点不
Do you know what time it is?
睡不着啊
Can't sleep.
睡不着吃点儿药呗
There are tabs for that.
那我就真睡着了
Yeah, but then I'd be sleeping.
又做梦了吗
Dreams again?
来打一架吗
Wanna fight?
我脚滑了
I slipped.
是啊  你脚滑
Right, you slipped
不是因为被我揍了一拳吗
as a result of me punching you in the face.
你只是在我滑的时候
I was already slipping
正好打了我一拳
when you happened to punch me in the face.
没什么联系
The two events were not related.
说说你做的梦
Tell me about this dream.
-有什么新内容吗  -没有
- Anything new? - No.
你得放下过去
You have to let go of the past.
我都不记得我的过去
I don't remember my past.
过去让你犹疑
It's causing you doubt,
犹疑使你脆弱
and doubt makes you vulnerable.
控制住
Control it.
你要是再失控
Lose control again, and you'll have to commune
就得去找至高智慧约谈了
with the Supreme Intelligence.
对一个战士来说  情绪才是最危险的
There's nothing more dangerous to a warrior than emotion.
幽默会让你分心
Humor is a distraction.
而愤怒
And anger?
愤怒只会让敌人有机可乘
Anger only serves the enemy.
距离上一波斯克鲁人进攻
One hundred twenty days
已有一百二十天
since the last Skrull attack.
真的有人
Has anyone ever seen
见过至高智慧长啥样吗
what the Supreme Intelligence really looks like?
没有人能得以瞻仰
No one can look upon the Supreme Intelligence
至高智慧的真容
in its true form.
明知故问
You know that.
我们的潜意识决定它们会以何种姿态显现
Our subconscious chooses the way they appear to us.
是很神圣  很私密的
So it's sacred. It's personal.
每个克里人都讳莫如深
No Kree divulges it, ever.
你看见的是什么
Who do you see?
-你的兄弟吗  -不是
- Your brother? - No.
-父亲吗  -不是
- Father? - No
-之前的指挥官  -弗斯
- Your old commander? - Vers.
你看到的是我  对吧
It's me you see, isn't it?
我知道你在干什么了
I see what you're trying to do.
-管用吗  -管用
- Is it working? - Yes.
但是转移话题是没用的
But you won't succeed in changing the subject.
你要是不想让我使用我的力量
What is the point of giving me these...
那为什么还要给我呢
if you don't want me to use them?
我想让你使用
I want you to use them.
至高智慧让我负责
The Supreme Intelligence gave me a responsibility...
教导你如何使用
of showing you how to use them.
我自己知道
I know how.
是吗  真是这样的话
Yeah, if that were true, you'd be able to
你不用你的力量也能打败我
knock me down without them.
控制你的冲动
Control your impulses.
别再用拳头思考  用用你的大脑
Stop using this, start using this.
我想让你成为最完美的你
I want you to be the best version of yourself.
至
高
智
慧
克
里
文
明
的
人
工
智
能
领
袖
弗斯
Vers.
至高智慧
Intelligence.
你的指挥官坚持认为你有资格出任务了
Your commander insists that you're fit to serve.
是的
I am.
但你还在与自己的情绪  与过去纠缠
You struggle with your emotions... with your past,
这样反而会让你越陷越深
which fuels them.
斯克鲁人进犯我们的帝国已达上百年
You are just one victim of the Skrull expansion...
你也只不过是其中的受害者之一
that has threatened our civilization for centuries.
这些侵略者悄悄渗入我们星球
Imposters who silently infiltrate...
然后一举攻占
then take over our planets.
你只记得其可怖
Horrors that you remember...
却不曾记起其它
and so much that you do not.
我的人生  都成了空白
It's all blank. My life.
你的形象本该是我心目中
You're supposed to take the form
最敬仰的人
of who I most admire...
但我甚至都不记得这个人和我有什么关系
but I don't even remember who this person was to me.
或许这是一种救赎
Perhaps this is a mercy
免你受到更多苦难
sparing you from a deeper pain.
让你为克里人的宿命做出贡献
Freeing you to do what all Kree must...
把人民的需求放在首位
put your people's needs before your own.
我们赐予了你一项伟大的能力
We've given you a great gift.
现在是你报答克里人的时候了
The chance to fight for the good of all Kree.
我愿意效忠
I want to serve.
那就控制好自己
Then master yourself.
我们能给你  那也能收回来
What was given can be taken away.
我不会让你失望的
I won't let you down.
马上就能见分晓了
We'll know soon enough.
你有一项任务
You have a mission.
带着荣耀完成它
Serve well, and with honor.
肯定不是什么好事
This can't be good.
肯定又是斯克鲁人
Must be another Skrull attack.
反正规模不小
Whatever it is, it's big.
你被斯克鲁人化形过吗
Has a Skrull ever simmed you?
有过一次
Once.
-相当不愉快的经历  -怎么
- It was deeply disturbing. - Why?
因为当我凝视着面前的死敌
Because I stared into the face of my mortal enemy...
我看到的是一张与我一模一样的脸
and the face staring back was my own.
你自己要是长得再好看点儿
Maybe if you were more attractive,
那也不是什么不愉快的经历了
then it would be less disturbing.
呵呵  你看我笑了吗
You think you're funny, but I'm not laughing.
你就没笑过
You never laugh.
我笑过  只不过不放在脸上
I laugh on the inside.
现在我没笑
I'm not doing that now.
还挺搞笑的  因为客观来讲
It's funny 'cause, objectively speaking,
你还挺帅的
you're quite handsome.
谢谢
Well, thank you.
听好了伙计们  正经点
Listen up, team. Knock it off.
好了
All right.
准备开始
Prepare for...
搜索营救我们的间谍索拉
a search and rescue of our spy, Soh-Larr.
斯克鲁人已经又攻下了一个星球
The Skrulls have invaded yet another border planet.
这次是托法星
This time, Torfa.
索拉给我们发来了警报
Soh-Larr sent us a warning.
但是信号被拦截了  他暴露了
The signal was intercepted, and his cover's blown.
斯克鲁将军塔洛斯
The Skrull general, Talos,
派出了杀手去找他
has sent kill units to find him.
要是被他们先找到
Should they reach him before we do...
这三年来他所掌握的情报
the intelligence he's acquired
几乎等于拱手相让了
over three years is as good as theirs.
指控者将在南部
The Accusers will bomb
轰炸一座斯克鲁人的堡垒
a Skrull stronghold here in the south.
我们潜入  找到索拉
We slip in, we locate Soh-Larr...
神不知鬼不觉地将他带离
and we get out, leaving them none the wiser.
至于托法星人
The Torfan populace.
我们不必与他们接触
We are not to interfere with them,
他们也不得干扰我们的任务
nor them with us.
本次行动安全至上
Nothing compromises the security of our mission.
一定要小心谨慎
Proceed with caution.
务必遵循指令  直至将目标救出来
Follow protocol before extracting him.
此次任务危机四伏
This is a dangerous mission.
命运若让我们命丧此日
We must all be ready to join the Collective
我们也当义无反顾
if that is our fate today.
为了克里星球
For the good of all Kree.
For the good of all Kree!
法
星
托
克
里
文
明
边
境
星
球
弗斯  追踪索拉的信号
Vers, track Soh-Larr's beacon.
阿特拉斯  米涅瓦  你们去占领高地
Att-Lass, Minn-Erva, find elevation.
外围地区发现托法人
Locals on the periphery.
大概有十多个
Maybe a dozen.
米涅瓦
Minn-Erva?
你听到了吗  有人收到吗
Do you read me? Does anybody copy?
请重复一遍
Repeat.
他的信号从那边的神殿传来  我们行动
His beacon's coming from that temple. Let's move.
不用了  这个地方很适合伏击
No. This is a perfect spot for an ambush.
进出都只有一条路
Only one way in, only one way out.
伏击的话能避免惊扰托法人
We can get past the locals.
况且我还不知道他们是不是托法人
We don't know if they are locals.
你那样太危险了
Too risky.
我自己去就行  不用你们陪同
You don't have to go with me. I'll go alone.
不  你不能去
No, you won't.
好吧  前提是我们不能离得太远
Right. We keep a close radius.
如果我们失去了联系  就在飞船碰头
We lose comms, we meet back at the Helion.
走吧
Come on.
阿特拉斯  你看到了吗
Att-Lass, you getting this?
收到  我看见了
Copy. I see them.
往后退
Get back!
指挥官
Commander?
往后退  快退
Get back! Back!
米涅瓦  你看得到现在的状况吗
Minn-Erva? Do you have eyes on this?
赶紧向后退  米涅瓦
Stay back. Minn-Erva
听得到我说话吗
Does anybody copy?
我不想伤害你们
I don't wanna hurt you.
后退
Keep back!
退远点
Stay back!
他们都是托法人  有两个还死掉了
They're locals. I found two dead.
里面没有斯克鲁人
No green.
他们就是饿坏了而已
They're just starving.
识别码 HGX-78
Hgx-78
TRT79-VVX6
Trt79-vvx6
后退
Get back.
他们是斯克鲁人
Skrulls!
弗斯
Vers!
弗斯  他们是斯克鲁人
Vers? Skrulls.
我们被埋伏了
It's an ambush.
敌方飞船靠近
Incoming!
快回飞船去
Back to the Helion.
弗斯  你收到了吗
Vers. Do you copy?
赶快回飞船去
Back to the Helion.
弗斯  请回答
Come in. Vers.
你怎么知道暗号的
How did you know the code?
这样吧  你给我讲讲你的秘密
How about I tell you my secret...
然后我再给你说说我的  如何
when you've told me yours?
我们来看看她脑子里有些什么秘密
Let's open her up.
这是哪儿
Where are we?
做好准备
Stand by.
你在想什么呢
Where's your head at?
不小心走了个神  你呢
In the clouds. Where's yours?
我可清醒的很
On my shoulders.
我要让男生们瞧瞧我们的厉害
About to show these boys how we do it.
你准备好了吗
You ready?
不就是更高  更远  更快嘛
Higher, further, faster, baby.
没错
That's right.
这是什么情况
This can't be right.
再往前回溯一些
Go back even further.
你开的太快了  你得减速
You're going too fast! You need to go slow!
这人是谁  我们在正确的
Who is this person? Are we in the right...?
你他妈到底怎么回事
What the hell are you thinking?
女孩儿根本就不适合玩这个
You don't belong out here!
我觉得我们好像回溯的有点过了
I think we went back too far.
你都让他玩了
You let him drive.
我试试看别的记忆
Let me try something.
你早该放弃了
Give up already!
你根本不适合玩这个
You don't belong out here!
你还远远不够格呢
You're not strong enough.
你这样只会害死自己
You'll kill yourself.
你永远也别想开飞机
They'll never let you fly.
在场的只有我一人迷茫吗
Am I the only one that's confused here?
你是一名不错的飞行员
You're a decent pilot.
但是你太过情绪化了
But you're too emotional.
你现在明白女人当不了飞行员了吧
You do know why they call it a cockpit, don't you?
一声巨响隆隆地响彻宇宙
A huge rumble throughout the cosmos
天上的太阳月亮和星星都为之颤动
shook the moon and the sun and the stars in the sky.
于是
And so,
小云雀掠过了整个夜空
little Alouette flew up throughout the night.
你看到了吗  是小云雀耶
Did you see her? It's Alouette.
快进屋子里  该吃饭啦
Get your butts inside, it's time to eat.
准备好起飞啦  淘气包上尉
Prepare for takeoff, Lieutenant Trouble.
多么美好的回忆
Charming memory.
等一下
Hang on.
我好像知道了
I think I've got it.
咕咕挺喜欢你的
Goose likes you.
她平时不怎么粘人的
She doesn't typically take to people.
你今天起的挺早的
Early start to your morning.
其实  我是熬夜熬到了现在
Uh, late night, actually.
有工作时  我一般睡不了觉
I can't sleep when there's work to do.
这句话听起来耳熟吧
Sound familiar?
试驾你的飞机不像是在工作
Flying your planes never feels like work.
风景挺美的  是吧
Wonderful view, isn't it?
我更喜欢在空中翱翔时的风景
I prefer the view from up there.
很快你就能体验到了  王牌驾驶员
You'll get there soon enough, Ace.
等等  就是她  让她回来
Wait! Wait, wait! That's her. Get her back.
正在准备中
Stand by.
这话听起来耳熟吧
Sound familiar?
风景挺美的  是吧
Wonderful view, isn't it?
我更喜欢在空中翱翔时的风景
I prefer the view from up there.
很快你就能体验到了  王牌驾驶员
You'll get there soon enough, Ace.
她衣服上写的什么
What's that on her shirt?
我看不清
I couldn't read it.
风景挺美的  是吧
Wonderful view, isn't it?
我更喜欢在空中翱翔时的风景
I prefer the view from up there.
-集中精力  -不好意思  你说什么
- Focus. - Excuse me?
向下看
Look down.
集中精力
Focus.
天马计划  温迪·劳森博士  就是她
"Pegasus. Dr. Wendy Lawson." That's her.
你也听得到这个声音吗
Do you hear that, too?
有没有她所在的位置
Do we have her location?
有了
Got it.
跟着劳森  看看能不能找到能量标志
Now track Lawson until we find the energy signature.
有点意思
Interesting.
等等
Huh. Hold on.
从这倒回去
Go back right before this. Go back.
好了  我看看你们是要去哪
This is it. Now let me see where you're headed.
来  看看坐标
That's right. Look at the coordinates.
专心
Focus.
把眼睛睁开
Open, please.
这就对了
That's it. That's it.
快好了
You're almost there.
快好了  别反抗了
You're almost there. Don't fight it.
专心
Focus!
让她回去  快让她回去
Get her back! Get her back now!
有什么有用的信息吗
Do we have any information we can act on?
劳森在C-53星球上
Just that Lawson was somewhere on planet C-53.
那我们就过去
We're on our way.
把那翻个底朝天也要把她找出来
Then dig, dig, dig deeper.
找到劳森才能找到光速引擎
Lawson is our link to that light-speed engine!
这对我们至关重要
And everything we're after.
刚才有反应了
That did something.
再试试
Try that again.
还不能杀她
Not yet!
你对我做了什么
What did you do to me?
我们就是找点信息
Now we're just after a little information.
你在我的脑子里植入了什么
What did you put in my head?
什么也没有
Nothing that wasn't already there.
但那些不是我的记忆
But those aren't my memories.
很不好受吧
Yeah, it's like a bad trip, isn't it?
你什么也想不起来很正常
I'm not surprised you can't keep it straight.
他们彻底改变了你
They really did a number on you.
别耍我了
Enough of your mind games.
你们想干什么
What do you want?
我们在找劳森博士的坐标
We're looking for the location of Dr. Lawson...
还有她的光速引擎
and her light-speed engine.
我根本不认识什么劳森博士
I don't know any Dr. Lawson.
是吗  那她为什么在你的记忆里
Really? Then why is she in your head?
你们知道怎么把这玩意弄掉吗
You guys wouldn't happen to know how these things come off, would ya?
不知道吗
No?
好吧
Fine.
你应该知道...
You do know why they call it a...
这么快就走了吗
You leaving so soon?
我们才刚认识呀
We're just getting to know each other.
C
-53
星
球
地
弗斯呼叫星际战队  能听到吗
Vers to Starforce command, do you read me?
有人吗
Hello? Do you copy?
嗨  我是弗斯  是克里星际战队的
Hi. I'm Vers. Kree Starforce.
这里是C-53星球吗
Is this C-53?
你能听懂吗  我的宇宙翻译器是不是坏了
Do you understand me? Is my universal translator working?
我能听懂
Yeah. I understand you.
太好了
Oh, good.
你负责这个区域的治安吗
Are you in charge of security for this district?
算是吧  除了电影院都是我负责
Sort of. Uh, the movie theater has its own guy.
我在哪能找到通讯设备
Where can I find communications equipment?
谢谢
Thank you.
追踪信号  找到她
Track the pod. Find the girl.
她知道的比她想的多
She knows more than she knows.
嘿
Hey.
这个我先挑了
This one's taken.
弗斯
Vers?
核对身份  CTC-39
Verify. CTC-39.
识别码  Grxv-1600
Grxv-1600
我挺好的  谢谢关心
And I'm fine, thank you for asking.
大家都还好吗  发生了什么
Is everyone okay? What happened?
斯克鲁人偷袭了我们
Skrull ambush.
我以为我们失去你了
I thought we'd lost you.
你找到索拉了吗
Did you find Soh-Larr?
那不是索拉
It wasn't Soh-Larr.
塔洛斯假扮成了他  还知道他的暗号
Talos simmed him. Even knew his code.
这不可能
That's impossible.
代码在他潜意识里
That code was buried in his unconscious.
斯克鲁人对我的记忆做了手脚
The Skrulls messed with my mind.
我觉得他们是通过那个机器
The machine that they used...
知道索拉的暗号的
I think it's how they extracted Soh-Larr's code.
弗斯  你在哪
Vers, where are you?
我在C-53星球
I'm on planet C-53.
斯克鲁人在找一个叫劳森的人
The Skrulls are looking for someone named Lawson.
谁
Who?
她是我在至高智慧面前看见的人
She's who I see.
什么
She's what?
弗斯
Vers?
你说什么
Vers, what?
她是个科学家
She's a scientist.
他们说她掌握了光速技术
They think that she's cracked the code on light-speed tech.
我要在他们之前找到她
I have to get to her before they do...
以免他们入侵别的星系
or else they'll be able to invade new galaxies.
不行  你已经被抓一次了
No. You've been caught once already.
C-53离我们多远
How far is C-53?
从最近的跳跃点过去要 22小时
Closest jump point is 22 hours.
弗斯  在我们来之前原地待命
Vers, hold your position until we get there.
保持信号方便我们联系你
Keep your comms online so we can contact you.
不行  如果他们抢先一步
No! What if they get a hold of it before...
抱歉
We're sorry.
您拨打的号码需要输入远程操控密码
A long-distance company access code is required for the number you have dialed.
-勇·罗格  -弗斯
- Yon-Rogg?  - Vers?
弗斯
Vers?
请输入密码后重新拨打
Please dial your call with the access code.
弗斯
Vers?
她可能被斯克鲁人控制了
If the Skrulls got to her, she's compromised.
她没你想的那么脆弱
She's stronger than you think.
你去过C-53吗
Ever been to C-53?
去过一次
Once.
那就是个鸟不拉屎的地方
It's a real shithole.
新来的  去问问那个保安
Hey, rookie! Go talk to the rent-a-cop.
是你报的警吗
Did you call this in?
信号已激活
Beacon activate
你好  小姐
Excuse me, miss.
你看没看见一位女士
You know anything about a lady blowing a hole...
把那边的音像店的房顶炸了个洞
through the roof of that Blockbuster over there?
有证人说她穿得像游戏人物
Witness says she was dressed for laser tag.
她应该往那边去了
Yeah, I think she went that way.
我想问你几个问题
Uh, I'd like to ask you some questions.
看来还得要把还录像带的地方告诉你
Maybe give you the 411 on the late-night drop box.
请问我能看看你的身份证明吗
Could I see some identification, please?
弗斯  克里星际战队
Vers. Kree Starforce.
我们的身份证明不是
We don't carry our identification
记录在小卡片上的
on little cards.
弗斯
Vers?
星际战队
Starforce?
你打算在镇上待多久
How long you plan to be in town?
我一追捕到
oh, I'll be out of your hair...
侵入你们星球的斯克鲁人
as soon as I track down the Skrulls
就立刻离开
that are infiltrating your planet.
斯克鲁人
Skrulls?
变形人吗
Shapeshifters?
他们可以变成任何生物的样子
They can transform into any life-form
连DNA都可以复制
down to the DNA.
小伙子们  你们不知道了吧
Oh, boy. You guys don't have any clue, do you?
等等哈
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hold on.
我们怎么知道你不是变形人的一员
How do we know you're not one of those shapeshifters?
特工弗瑞  恭喜你了
Congratulations, Agent Fury.
终于搞清楚状况了
You have finally asked a relevant question.
不  应该我恭喜你  星际女战士
No! Congratulations to you, Starforce lady.
你被捕了
You're under arrest.
新人
Rook!
新人  我们走
Rook, let's roll!
你看到她的武器了吗
Did you see her weapon?
没有
I did not.
小心点
Watch it!
嫌疑人在北上的电车上  正在追踪
Suspect on northbound train. In pursuit.
相信我  真正的信徒  相信我
Trust me, true believer.Trust me.
相信我  真正的信徒
Trust me, true believer.
下车
Get off!
电车马上就要进入前面的隧道了
Train's heading for a tunnel up ahead.
我们去车站会会他们吧
Let's greet them at the station.
弗瑞先生  我是特工科尔森
Mr. Fury, this is Agent Coulson.
我还在音像店这里
Uh, I'm still here at the Blockbuster.
你们都去哪里了
And, uh, where'd everybody go?
我刚收集完证据
I finished collecting evidence...
快叫救护车
We need an ambulance!
谁打一下911
Someone call 911!
天呐  大家都还好吧
Oh, my gosh! Is everyone okay?
还有谁看到那个东西了吗
Anyone else see that?
神盾局公务  请退后
Official S.H.I.E.L.D. activity. Stay back.
潜水服不错哈
Nice scuba suit.
开心点嘛  亲爱的
Lighten up, honey, huh?
笑一笑嘛
Got a smile for me?
真是个怪人
Freak.
地球上都是碳基生物  这家伙却不是
All life on Earth is carbon-based. Not this guy.
不管他以什么为食
Whatever he runs on,
元素周期表里肯定都没有
it's not on the periodic table.
你的意思是他是外星人
You're saying he's not from around here?
你的眼睛怎么了
Hey, how's your eye?
没事
Well, I'd say fine...
但我不敢相信眼前所见到的
but it can't believe what it's seeing.
你觉得这东西长得像科尔森吗
You say this thing looked like Coulson?
嗯  而且说话的方式也很像
Mmm. Talked like him, too.
那个女人说还有很多这种生物进入地球了
And the woman said that there were more?
她用的是侵入这个词
The word she used was "infiltration."
你相信她吗
You believe her?
看到这个就信了
Not till I saw this.
计划是什么
What's your plan?
我去找那个音像店女孩
I'll find Blockbuster girl.
我接到报案  有个偷车贼
I got word on a motorcycle thief
符合她的形象
that fits her description.
如果她能告诉我们
If she can tell us
这些绿蜥蜴出现在这里的理由
why these lizards are here...
那么有可能她也知道怎么把他们赶出去
maybe she can tell us how to kick 'em to the curb.
好的
Good.
但我们得单独完成任务
Do it alone, though.
不能相信任何人
We can't trust anyone.
哪怕是自己人
Not even our own men.
是  长官
Yes, sir.
真是奇丑无比的野兽  对吧
Wow. They're ugly bastards, aren't they?
确实没有布拉德·皮特帅
Yeah, well, he's no Brad Pitt, sir.
一路走好  我的朋友
Safe journey to the beyond, my friend.
我会完成我们的使命
I will finish what we started.
最好别靠太近  老大
I wouldn't get too close there, boss.
别放任何人进出就行
No one in or out.
你需要什么
What can I get ya?
这张照片是在哪里照的
Where was this photograph taken?
在一个机场照的
An airport.
天马计划在哪儿
Where's Pegasus?
那是机密
That's classified.
和我查到的关于你的资料一样
Not unlike the file I started on you.
但是你倒是改变了一点儿
But I see you've changed it up a bit since then.
街边的便宜货很适合你
Grunge is a good look for you.
你这一天过得很辛苦吧  特工弗瑞
Did you have a rough day, Agent Fury?
我觉得挺酷炫的
It was cool, you know?
经历了一场外星人入侵  飞车追逐
Had a space invasion, big car chase.
还得观看外星人尸检
Got to watch an alien autopsy.
典型的朝九晚五啊
Typical nine-to-five.
所以你看到了一个外星人咯
So you saw one?
我从来不相信外星人的存在
I was never one to believe in aliens...
但我都亲眼看到了
but I can't unsee that.
可能会有一点尴尬  但我还是想问一下
This is gonna get a little awkward, but I gotta ask.
你觉得我也是绿蜥蜴中的一员
You think I'm one of those green things.
小心驶得万年船
Can't be too careful.
我是百分百的地球人
You are looking at 100% red-blooded Earth man.
恐怕你得拿出证据证明一下
I'm afraid I'm gonna need proof.
你是要我的皮肤取样还是尿液样本
We talking cheek swab or urine sample?
没用  他们会复制DNA
No. The DNA would match.
想要我的聊天室的密码吗
Want my AOL password?
斯克鲁人只能获取
Skrulls can only sim recent memories
宿主最近的记忆
of their host bodies.
你想要我的私人信息
You wanna get personal.
你在哪儿出生的
Where were you born?
阿拉巴马州  豪斯威尔
Huntsville, Alabama.
严格上说  我不太记得了
But technically, I don't remember that part.
-你第一只宠物的名字  -斯鲁夫先生
- Name of your first pet? - Mr. Snoofers.
-斯鲁夫先生  -对啊
- Mr. Snoofers? - That's what I said.
我通过测试了吗
Do I pass?
还没有  第一份工作是什么
Not yet. First job?
士兵  我高中一毕业就去当兵了
Soldier. Straight out of high school.
被授予了陆军上校军衔
Left the ranks a full bird colonel.
-之后呢  -间谍
- Then? - Spy.
-在哪儿当间谍  -那是在冷战时期
- Where? - It was the Cold War.
我们几乎哪儿都得去
We were everywhere.
贝尔法斯特  布加勒斯特
Uh, Belfast. Bucharest.
贝尔格莱德  布达佩斯
Belgrade. Budapest.
我喜欢这些B开头的词  完美押韵
I like the B's. I can make them rhyme.
-现在呢  -坐了六年办公室
- Now? - Been riding a desk for the past six years...
研究未来的敌人
trying to figure out where our
会来自什么地方
future enemies are coming from.
但我从没想过
Never occurred to me
他们会从天而降
they would be coming from above.
说出一个斯克鲁人编不出来的怪毛病
Name a detail so bizarre a Skrull could never fabricate it.
我不吃斜着切的面包
If toast is cut diagonally, I can't eat it.
你没必要问这个  不是吗
You didn't need that, did you?
不  不  没必要  但是我喜欢
No. No, I didn't. But I enjoyed it.
好  到你了
Okay. Your turn.
证明你不是斯克鲁人
Prove you're not a Skrull.
这怎么能够向我证明
And how is that supposed to prove to me
你不是斯克鲁人呢
you're not a Skrull?
这是光子能量波
That's a photon blast.
所以呢
And?
斯克鲁人可不会这个
A Skrull can't do that.
所以  你从军队上校
So, a full bird colonel
到间谍再到神盾局特工
turned spy turned S.H.I.E.L.D. agent...
肯定有很高的安全级别
must have pretty high security clearance.
天马计划在哪
Where's Pegasus?
斯克鲁人会变形成其他生物
Okay. The Skrulls sim alien races
渗入并占领他们的星球
to infiltrate and take over planets.
而你是克里人  高贵的战斗民族
And you're a Kree? A race of noble warriors?
英雄  高贵的战斗英雄
Heroes. Noble warrior heroes.
那么  斯克鲁人找劳森博士做什么
So, um, what do Skrulls want with Dr. Lawson?
他们认为她在天马计划中
They believe that she developed
发明了光速引擎
a light-speed engine at Pegasus.
光速引擎
Light-speed engine?
我得承认这还不是今天听到的最疯狂的事
Gotta admit, that's not the craziest thing I've heard today.
这个嘛  天色还早呢
Well, it's still early.
你呢  你想要什么
And you, what do you want?
在斯克鲁人势不可当之前阻止他们
To stop the Skrulls before they become unstoppable.
还有呢
And?
听着  战争是宇宙通用语言
Look, war is a universal language.
我一眼就能看出离群的士兵
I know a rogue soldier when I see one.
你来是有个人原因的
You got a personal stake in this.
这里是政府领地
This is government property.
请掉头离开
Turn your vehicle around.
尼古拉斯·约瑟夫·弗瑞  神盾局特工
Nicholas Joseph Fury. Agent of S.H.I.E.L.D.
拇指放在识别器上
Place your thumb on the pad.
稍等
One moment.
尼古拉斯·约瑟夫·弗瑞
Nicholas Joseph Fury.
你有三个名字吗
You have three names?
大家都叫我弗瑞
Everybody calls me Fury.
不叫尼古拉斯  约瑟夫
Not Nicholas. Not Joseph.
或者尼克  就叫弗瑞
Not Nick. Just Fury.
-你妈叫你什么  -弗瑞
- What does your mom call you? - Fury.
-那你叫她什么  -弗瑞
- What do you call her? - Fury.
你的孩子呢
What about your kids?
如果我有的话  他们会叫我弗瑞
If I have them, they'll call me Fury.
准许进入
You are cleared for access.
谢谢
Thank you.
美
国
宇
航
局
暨
空
军
联
合
设
施
天
马
计
划
等一下
Oh, hold up.
你穿得像个青春期叛逆侄女
You look like somebody's disaffected niece.
把它戴上
Put that on.
-这是什么  -神盾局的标志
- What is it? - It's the S.H.I.E.L.D. logo.
戴着印着标志的帽子
Does, uh, announcing your identity on clothing
执行秘密任务真的好吗
help with the covert part of your job?
你个穿着橡胶战服的太空战士也好意思说
Said the space soldier who was wearing a rubber suit.
把衬衣拿下来
Lose the flannel.
你们有什么事吗
How can I help you?
我们是神盾局特工
We're agents of S.H.I.E.L.D.
我们在找一位叫劳森的女士
We're looking for a woman named Lawson.
一位博士  温迪·劳森
A Dr. Wendy Lawson.
你认识她吗
Do you know her?
跟我来
Follow me.
你有没有听过有朋自远方来这句话
You familiar with the phrase "welcome wagon"?
没有
No.
我们显然没被当成朋友
Well, this ain't it.
那是通讯器吗
Is that a communicator?
对  最新型的双向传呼机
Yeah. State-of-the-art two-way pager.
你在呼叫谁
Who are you paging?
我妈  别担心  我没提到你
My mom. Don't worry. I didn't mention you.
我和目标被扣留了  需要支援
你先请
After you.
技术不错
Impressive.
你该看看我用回形针更厉害
Oh, you should see what I can do with a paperclip.
嘿  小可爱  你好吗
Hey, there. How are you?
我的妈呀  看看你
Oh, my goodness. Look at you. Just look at you.
你是不是最可爱的小猫咪呀
Aren't you the cutest little thing?
是不是呀  你叫什么名字呢
Aren't you cute? And what's your name, huh?
叫什么名字
What's your name?
咕咕  酷名配酷猫
"Goose." Cool name for a cool cat.
弗瑞
Fury?
我一会儿回来
I'll be back.
让我把指纹拿出来
Oh! Let me get my fingerprint out.
先揭开胶带
Just let me unravel this puppy.
你刚才坐着看我玩胶带的时候
You sat there and watched me play with tape?
明明可以直接
When all you had to do was...
我可不想抢了你的风头
I didn't wanna steal your thunder.
劳森
Huh. Lawson.
劳森的光速引擎设计图
Lawson's plan for the light-speed engine.
我好奇他们为什么终止这个项目
I wonder why they terminated the project.
可能因为她是个疯子
Um, maybe because she's cuckoo.
克里文字吗
Kree glyphs?
劳森不是疯子
Lawson is not cuckoo.
她是克里人
She's Kree.
她已经死了
Well, she's dead.
什么
What?
她未经允许试飞原型机
She crashed the Asis aircraft
结果坠机身亡
doing an unauthorized test flight.
还害死了一位飞行员
Took a pilot down with her.
这就是保安对我们不友好的原因
That's why security here is so unfriendly.
他们在掩盖一个十亿美元的错误
They're covering up a billion-dollar mistake.
你的光速引擎也跟着完蛋了
Oh, and your light-speed engine is toast.
坠机是什么时候发生的
When did this crash happen?
六年前  1989年
Six years ago. 1989.
那位飞行员是谁
Who was the pilot?
大部分记录都被涂黑了
Um, most of this thing's redacted...
不过这儿有一封玛利亚·兰博的推荐信
but there is a testimonial here from a Maria Rambeau.
她们生前见的最后一个人
Last person to see them alive.
你还好吗
You okay?
我马上回来
Back in a minute.
这不是为了打仗
This isn't about fighting wars.
是为了结束战争
It's about ending them.
我知道劳森是克里人
I know Lawson was Kree.
她是在C-53星球上然后死于飞机失事
She was here on C-53 and died in a plane crash.
你知道这件事吗
Do you know anything about this?
我刚找到一份旧的任务报告
I just discovered a mission report
从C-53星球发出的
sent from C-53.
我的权限内只能告诉你这么多  但弗斯
There's only so much I'm cleared to tell you, Vers, but...
劳森其实是代号玛威尔的秘密特工
Lawson was an undercover Kree operative named Mar-Vell.
她过去在研究一种独特的能量核心
She was working on a unique energy core.
一项显然对我们赢得战争有利的技术实验
Experimenting with tech that apparently could help us win the war.
她还在这吗
She still here?
她很配合调查  长官
She's cooperating with the investigation, sir.
-你的人都留在这里  -是  长官
- You men stay here.  -  Yes, sir.
我想单独讯问她
I want to question her alone.
干得好  尼古拉斯
Excellent work, Nicholas.
报告上有提到我吗
Does it say anything about me?
提到你  不  当然没有
Anything about you? No, of course not.
怎么会有呢
Why would it?
我找到一些我曾经在这里生活过的证据
I found evidence that I had a life here.
在C-53星球
On c-53?
我在至高智慧面前看到的影像就是玛威尔
Mar-Vell is who I see when I visit the Supreme Intelligence.
我感觉认识她  我印象中她就是劳森
I knew her. And I knew her as Lawson.
听起来像是斯克鲁人搞的鬼  弗斯
This sounds like Skrull simulation, Vers.
不  不是  我记得我在这里生活过
No, it's not. Because I remember. I was here.
别乱想  记住你的训练
Stop. Remember your training.
去了解你的敌人  有时候那会是你自己
Know your enemy. It could be you.
不要让你的情绪影响了你的判断
Do not let your emotions override your judgment.
她在地下第六层
She's on sublevel six.
我在五层下 去守楼梯  以防她逃跑
I'll get off on five... and take the stairs in case she makes a run for it.
像我们在哈瓦那那样瓮中捉鳖
Do a pincer move like we did in Havana.
没错  就像我们那次在哈瓦那一样
Right. Like we did in Havana.
我们快到跳跃点了
We're nearing the jump point.
把你的信号打开方便我能找到你
Leave your beacon on so I can find you.
我们会彻底查清楚这件事的  弗斯
We'll get to the bottom of this, Vers.
一起
Together.
好的
Okay.
弗斯
Vers!
弗瑞跟目标有勾结
Fury's colluding with the target.
那他为什么要叫我们来
Then why would he call us in?
我只知道上面命令把他也带回去
All I know is we take him in, too.
不论死活
Dead or alive.
不论死活吗
Dead or alive?
快  快  快
Go. Go, go!
是我哪里说错话了吗
Was it something I said?
其实  我不是真的需要戴眼镜才能看清
Now, you know, I don't really need these to see...
只不过戴上眼镜看上去更人模狗样
but they do kinda complete the look.
你不觉得吗
Don't you think?
是你叫他们来的吗
You called them in?
我的错
My bad.
科尔森  你看到他们了吗
Coulson, do you have eyes on them?
他们不在下面
They're not down here.
我们上去找找
Let's try up there.
-什么  -你的对讲器
- What?  - Your communicator.
很显然不能信任你拿着它
You obviously can't be trusted with it.
你知道怎么驾驶这东西吗
Do you know how to fly this thing?
我看看
Uh, we'll see.
要么是  要么死
That's a yes or no question.
是
Yes.
我就说这才像话
That's what I'm talking about!
我们有一个小小的偷渡成员
We got a stowaway.
抓稳了  咕咕
Hang on, Goose.
咕咕
Goose.
不  咕咕
No, Goose.
谁是一只好猫咪呀  咕咕对不对
Who's a good kitty, huh? Huh, Goose?
是的  没错
Yes, that's right.
咕咕就是一只好猫咪
Who's a good kitty, Goose?
你是好猫咪  没错
You the good kitty, that's right.
上面有你认识的人吗
See anyone you know?
趣事
Funny story.
我到哈拉时半死不活  完全没有记忆
I arrived on Hala near dead. No memory.
那是六年前的事了
That was six years ago.
所以
So,
你觉得你是劳森博士飞机失事时的飞行员
you think you're the pilot that went down with Dr. Lawson?
我是说最后一个看到他们活着的人
I'm saying the last person to see them alive
可能可以告诉我们真相
could probably tell us.
-玛利亚·兰博吗  -对
-Maria Rambeau? - Mm-hmm.
好  那么我们怎么能到路易斯安那
So, how do we get to Louisiana?
往正东开  然后在孟菲斯向右转
Due east. Hang a right at Memphis.
那个特工  阻止了斯克鲁人的那个
That agent... that stopped the Skrulls from finding us?
你说科尔森吗  他是新来的
Coulson. The new guy.
所以我想他还不怎么讨厌我
I guess he doesn't hate me yet.
给他点时间
Yeah, well, give him time.
我觉得他是一个直觉型的  你知道吗
I guess he had a feeling, you know?
他敢凭直觉判断而违背命令
Went with his gut against orders.
这个真的很难做到
That's a really hard thing to do.
也许这就是我们人性的一面吧
But it's what keeps us human.
我经常因为这个惹麻烦  真的很多次
I get in trouble for that. A lot.
看得出来
Oh, I can see that about you.
救一个把你卖给斯克鲁人的家伙
Rescuing the guy who sold you out to the Skrulls?
我猜那可不是克里人的规范操作
I'm guessing that's not standard Kree operating procedure.
如果你不告我的老板  我就不告你的
Well, I won't tell your boss if you don't tell mine.
罗南
Ronan.
指控者完成了他们的行动
The Accusers completed their operation...
但是总的来说  任务是失败的
but the greater mission was a failure,
拜你的团队所赐
thanks to your team.
那是个陷阱  把我们的特工弗斯
It was a trap to lure our operative Vers
引诱到托法去然后好绑架她
to Torfa and kidnap her.
把他们的位置告诉我们
Give us their location.
我们会处理好恐怖分子的威胁的
We'll take care of the terrorist threat.
把他们炸出银河系吗
By bombing them out of the galaxy?
不  我们会处理的
No, we'll handle this.
任何地方哪怕只有一个斯克鲁人的细胞
A cell of Skrulls anywhere
对任何一个克里人来说都是一种威胁
is a threat to Kree everywhere.
他们到底在哪
Where are they?
-他们在  -目前信号丢失了
- They are...   - Lost.
目前他们信号丢失了
They are lost for now.
但我们肯定会找到他们的
But we will find them.
最好能  不然我们亲自去找
Do so, or we will.
保持去C-53星球的航线
Maintain the course for C-53.
打扰了  我想找一个叫玛丽亚·兰博的
Excuse me, I'm looking for Maria Rambeau.
卡罗尔阿姨
Auntie Carol?
妈妈  是卡罗尔阿姨
Mom, it's Auntie Carol!
我就知道  他们都说你死了
I knew it! Everyone said you were dead!
但我们知道他们在骗人
But we knew they were lying.
我不再是你认识的那个我了
I'm not really who you think I am.
这是我听过的最扯的胡话
That is the craziest shit I ever heard.
绿色的变身外星人  哪有这种东西
Green transforming aliens? There's no such thing.
你说的没错  小姐
You are absolutely right, young lady.
没这种东西
There is no such thing.
因为  如果有的话
'Cause if there were,
我们肯定会想抓回来占为已有的
we would want to keep that to ourselves.
你不相信我吗
You don't believe me?
不是吧
No way!
太帅了
That's so cool!
她那双手除了烧水
Oh, she can do a lot more than make tea
能做的事可多呢
with those hands.
比如呢  让我们看看
Like what? Show us.
以后再说吧
Maybe later.
我这有你的东西
I kept all your stuff.
我去拿
I'll go get it.
你不去帮帮她吗
You want to give her a hand with that?
你什么都不记得了吗
You don't remember anything?
只有一些片段
I see flashes.
一些瞬间
Little moments.
但我不知道是不是真的
But I can't tell what's real.
如果我能把那天早上的事全都记起来
If I could just piece together what happened that morning...
也许一切就都清晰了
maybe it'll all make sense.
你一大早来敲门把我弄醒了
You woke me up banging on my door at dawn.
你总这么干
Your usual move.
那时候  我们得早起
Back then, we had to get up so early.
空军部本不让女人去飞行战斗
The Air Force still wasn't letting women fly combat...
所以测试劳森的飞机是我们唯一
so testing Lawson's planes was our only shot
能做的有意义的事
at doing something that mattered.
你想开着旧野马跟我比赛谁先到基地
You wanted to race to base in your old Mustang...
我也没打算阻止你
and I wasn't about to argue,
因为我知道我的科迈罗会嬴
'cause I knew my Camaro would dominate.
但你作弊了  你抄近路
But you cheated, took a shortcut.
抄近路怎么就算作弊了
Since when is a shortcut cheating?
因为那违反了我们的赛前约定
Since it violates the predetermined rules of engagement.
我真的不记得了
I definitely don't remember those.
你当然不记得了
Hmm. Of course you don't.
当我到达机库时  劳森很惊慌
When I got to the hangar, Lawson was agitated.
她说她赶着去救命
She said she had lives to save.
她本想亲自操控
She was trying to take the Asis up herself,
但是你说
but you said that...
如果有人命在旦夕  让我来
If there were lives at stake, I would fly the plane.
是的  是的  英雄时刻
Yeah. Yep. Big hero moment.
这是我们俩都期待的机会
The kind of moment we'd both been waiting for.
博士总是那么特别  所以我们才崇拜她
The doc was always unique. That's why we liked her.
现在你却说她来自外星
But now you're saying she's from another planet.
我知道让你相信这个很难
I know this must be hard for you.
哪个部分  你刚刚说的这部分吗
Oh, what? This part right here?
不  不
No. No. Mmm-mmm.
难的是  在秘密任务中
Oh, what's hard is losing my best friend...
失去我最好的朋友
in a mission so secret
却要表现的像什么都没发生一样
they act like it never even happened.
难的是  让自已相信你还在某个地方
Hard is knowing you were out there somewhere
顽强的活着
too damn stubborn to die.
而六年后的今天你又出现在这
And now you come up in here after six years...
双手冒着火星
with your supercharged fire hands...
你还想让我叫你
and you expect me to call you...
我不知道该叫你什么  弗斯
I don't even know what. Vers?
那才是真的你吗
Is that really who you are now?
我不知道
I don't know.
来看啊
Come look!
这是你跟我在万圣节时的照片
This is me and you on Halloween.
我扮成了阿梅莉亚·埃尔哈特
I'm Amelia Earhart and
Amelia Earhart是一名飞行员 Janis Joplin是一名摇滚音乐家
你扮成了詹尼斯·乔普林
you're Janis Joplin.
这是你小的时候
Oh, this is you when you were little.
你跟家里的关系不好
You didn't get along with your parents...
妈妈说我们就是你的家人
so Mom said we became your real family.
这是圣诞节的照片
This is us on Christmas.
我得到了我最喜欢的兔子拖鞋
I got my favorite bunny slippers.
这是你小时候的另一张照片
This is another picture of you when you were little.
你一直想当个飞行员
You've always wanted to be a pilot.
这是你刚毕业时的照片
And this is right after you graduated.
这是你圣诞节得到的小狗
This was your dog that you got for Christmas...
这是你们空军全体人员的照片
This is a picture of everybody from your Air Force team.
这是你和我妈妈
And this is you with Mom
刚参加了一天的培训
right after a good day of training.
这三个人是你最欣赏的
These were your three favorite guys.
等等  我忘了一件事
Oh, wait. I forgot.
你的外套
Your jacket.
自从我把番茄酱弄到上面去之后
Mom doesn't let me wear it anymore
妈妈就不让我穿了
after I spilled ketchup on it.
这是那次事故之后唯一留下来的东西
That was all that survived the crash.
至少我们认为是
Or so we thought.
别开门
Don't answer that.
只是邻居而已
It's just my neighbor.
他们可以变成认何人
They can change into anyone.
嗨  你好
Hi there.
你想干嘛
What do you want?
嘿  汤姆
Uh... Hey, Tom.
这是我朋友  卡罗尔
This is my friend, Carol.
很高兴见到你
Oh. Pleased to meet you.
哎呀
Yowzers.
静电也是很疼的
Static electricity out here's no joke.
我注意到你停在路边的那只奇怪的鸟
I noticed that peculiar bird you got parked by the road...
我在想
and I was just wondering...
你是否介意我带孩子们去
if you mind if I bring the boys over
做一次近距离观察
to get a closer look-see?
-一次近距离观察 -是的
- A closer look-see? -Yeah.
去看看停在路边的鸟
To see the "bird" parked out by the road?
为了想出这么个理由
You're really working overtime
你没少花时间吧  塔洛斯
to sell this one, aren't you, Talos?
不好意思  汤姆  今天不太方便
I'm sorry, Tom. This really isn't a good time.
我明天去找你  好吗
I'll come by tomorrow, okay?
好的
Uh... Okay.
你知道吗  你真应该对邻居友好点
You know, you really should be kinder to your neighbors.
因为你不知道你什么时候
You never know when you're gonna need
会找邻居帮忙
to borrow some sugar.
等等
Now, hang on a second.
在你挥手出招
Before you go swinging those jazz hands around...
毁了你朋友房子之前
making a mess of your friend's house...
房子不错  小姐
It's a lovely home, miss.
天哪
Oh, my God!
什么鬼
What the hell?
不会有人伤害那小姑娘的
No one's gonna hurt the girl.
别杀我
Just don't kill me.
那样的话真会使情况更复杂
That would really complicate the situation.
再过五秒我就爆了你的头
I'm about five seconds from complicating that wall
让斯克鲁人的脑浆溅满整面墙
with some ugly-ass Skrull brains.
我很抱歉我变成了你老大的样子
I'm sorry I simmed your boss.
但现在我以真实的自己毫无保留地
But now I stand before you as my true self.
站在你面前
Without deception.
那外面的人是谁
And who is that out there?
好吧  这么说也有道理
Okay, that's a fair point...
但是我确信你明白
but I'm sure that you understand
我必须采取一些预防措施
I had to take some precautions.
我看见你在双手被困住的情况下
I saw you crush 20 of my best men
打败了我最强的20个手下
with your hands bound.
我只想和你谈谈
I just wanna talk.
上次我们谈话的时候
Last time we talked,
我被大头朝下吊了起来
I ended up hanging from my ankles.
那个时候我还不知道你是谁
That was before I knew who you were.
不知道是什么把你变得与众不同
Before I knew what made you different from the others.
我有你六年前在天马计划中
I have an audio recording from Pegasus...
飞机失事时的录音
of your voice from a plane crash six years ago...
是从一个你们叫做黑匣子的装置里得到的
on a device I believe you call a "black box."
他们告诉我它在坠机中被毁了
They told me it was destroyed in the crash.
你是怎么得到的
How'd you get it?
她不明白
She don't understand.
小姐  我有一项特殊的技能
Young lady, I have a special skill...
它允许我进入到
that kind of allows me
我不应该去的地方
to get into places I'm not supposed to be.
你再叫我小姐
Call me "young lady" again...
我要把脚放在
I'm gonna put my foot in a place
它不应该在的地方
it's not supposed to be.
我应该猜一下是哪儿吗
Am I supposed to guess where that is?
你的屁股
Your ass.
我明白了  我们之间的气氛有点紧张
Okay, I get it. We're all a little on edge here.
但是我真的  只是需要你的帮助
But, look, I just need your help
解码一些坐标
decoding some coordinates.
如果你愿意坐下来听听录音的话
If you'll sit down and you'll listen to this...
我向你保证  你不会白费时间
I assure you, it'll be worth your while.
把你手下叫到里面  我会听的
Call your buddy back inside and I'll listen.
成交
Deal.
我的天哪  把那家伙赶走
Oh, my God! Get that thing away.
它是怎么进来的
How'd that get in here?
这只猫吗
The cat?
你该不会害怕喵星人吧
This isn't what you're afraid of, is it?
它不是一只猫
That's not a cat.
-那是噬元兽  -噬元兽
- That's a Flerken. - A Flerken?
妈
Mom?
莫妮卡
Monica.
-为什么我不能一起听  -安静
- Why can't I listen, too? - Shh!
发生什么了
What's happening?
它在加载
It's loading.
输入坐标
Punch in the coordinates
5229  负4-7  8.7-6-8  0.2
5-2-2-9, negative 4-7, 8.7-6-8, 0.2.
收到  你要去哪儿  博士
Copy that. Where are we going, Doc?
我的实验室
My laboratory.
你的实验室  这是什么意思
Your laboratory? What do you mean?
不
Oh, no.
那是  等等  那是什么
Is that... Wait, what is that?
我的雷达上看不见它
It's not showing up on my radar.
走  卡罗尔  快飞
Go, Carol. Fly!
那不是米格飞机  劳森
That's no MiG, Lawson.
他们到底是谁
Who the hell are they?
他们是坏蛋  加速  快点
Those are the bad guys. Fly faster now!
收到  长官
Yes, ma'am.
-他们想要什么  -我  我的成果
- What do they want? - Me. My work.
我不该带你一起来
I never should have brought you along.
坐稳  加速了
Here come some G's.
他们在向后射击  抓稳了
They're firing backwards. Hold on!
跳伞  快跳  快快快
Bail out! Bail out! Bail out!
坚持住  劳森
Stay with me, Lawson!
卡罗尔  说话  能听到吗
Carol, come in. Do you copy?
是的  我收到了  我们撞到地面了
Yeah, I copy. We hit ground.
卡罗尔  你没事吧 收到了吗
Carol, are you okay? Do you copy?
是的  收到
Yeah! I copy.
博士
Doc?
你的血
Your blood.
是蓝色的
It's blue.
是的  但是  我发型怎么样
Yeah, but, uh, how's my hair?
帮我出来  可以吗
Help me out, will ya?
我得在他们到这儿之前毁了它
I gotta destroy it before they get here.
劳森
Lawson?
你还记得我说过我们在这里的工作吗
You remember what I said about our work here?
是用于什么的
What it's for?
用来结束战争吗
To end wars?
是的  但是战争比你想的规模还要大
Yeah. But the wars are bigger than you know.
该死的
Damn it!
我的名字不是劳森
My name is not Lawson.
我真正的名字是玛威尔
My real name is Mar-Vell,
我来自一个叫哈拉的星球
and I come from a planet called Hala.
如果不是我们被一艘飞船击落
I would say that you're delusional...
而且你的血是蓝色的话
but we just got shot down by a spaceship
我会觉得你是个幻想狂
and your blood is blue.
听着  我半辈子都在打一场可耻的战争
Listen, I spent half my life fighting a shameful war.
现在  在你让我更后悔之前
Now, skedaddle before you give me
赶紧逃跑
any more regrets.
但是要记住坐标  好吗
Just remember the coordinates, okay?
你得在没有我的情况下救他们
You gotta save 'em without me.
拯救谁  怎么救
Save who? How?
现在我得在他们找到之前把引擎毁掉
Now I gotta blow this engine before they find it.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
我们不想伤害你
We have no interest in hurting you.
不想伤害我们吗
No?
那你一见面就开枪是什么意思
'Cause all the shooting kinda gave me the wrong impression!
能量核心
The energy core.
在哪里
Where is it?
救护队在路上了
Pararescue's on the way.
再过两分钟你就会被包围
You have two minutes until you're surrounded.
我看我们也没有理由继续这段对话了
Then I see no reason to prolong this conversation.
不  等等
No, wait!
你是说能量核心吗
You mean that energy core?
不
No!
指挥官  她还在动  请允许开火
Commander? She's still moving. Permission to fire.
别开枪
Hold your fire.
什么都没留下
There's nothing left.
核心已经被摧毁了
The core has been destroyed.
她吸收了它的能量
She absorbed its power.
把她一起带走
She's coming with us.
他骗了我
He lied to me.
我所知道的每一件事  都是谎言
Everything that I knew was a lie.
现在  你明白了
Now, you understand.
什么  我现在明白什么了
What? What do I understand now?
勇·罗格杀死了玛威尔
Yon-Rogg killed Mar-Vell.
他杀了她
He killed her...
因为她发现她在
'cause she found out that she was
一场不义之战中站在了错误的一方
on the wrong side of an unjust war.
不
No.
你的人是恐怖分子
Your people are terrorists.
他们杀死无辜的人
They kill innocents.
我见过托法的废墟
I saw the ruins on Torfa.
那些废墟是指控者造成的
Ruins that the Accusers are responsible for.
在托法星  我的人民以难民的身份活着
My people lived as refugees on Torfa.
自从我们开始反抗克里人的统治
Homeless, ever since we
他们便摧毁了我们的星球
resisted Kree rule...
导致我们无家可归
and they destroyed our planet.
我们剩下的这一小撮人
And the handful of us that are left
接下来也会被屠杀
will be slaughtered next...
除非你帮我完成玛威尔开始的研究
unless you help me finish what Mar-Vell started.
她找到的能量核心
The core that she found
可以给光速飞船提供动力
would have powered a light-speed ship...
能够把我们带到安全的地方
capable of carrying us to safety.
一个新家  一个克里人找不到的  家
A new home where the Kree can't reach us.
劳森总是告诉我们
Lawson always told us that
我们在天马计划里的工作
our work at Pegasus
不是为了战争
wasn't to fight wars...
而是为了结束战争
but to end them.
她想让你帮我们找到能量核心
She wanted you to help us find the core.
我已经把它毁掉了
Well, I already destroyed it.
不  你毁掉的是引擎
No, you destroyed the engine.
给它提供动力的能量核心
The core that powered it
在一个遥远的地方
is in a remote location.
如果你能帮我们解码了这些坐标
If you help us decode those coordinates...
我们就能找到它
we can find it.
你会用它来摧毁我们的
You'll use it to destroy us.
我们只是想要一个家
We just want a home.
你和我都因为克里人失去了一切
You and I lost everything at the hands of the Kree.
你现在还不明白吗
Can't you see it now?
你不是他们中的一员
You're not one of them.
你不了解我
You don't know me.
你根本不知道我是谁
You have no idea who I am.
连我  也不知道我是谁
I don't even know who I am!
你是卡罗尔·丹弗斯
You are Carol Danvers.
你是黑匣子里那个
You are the woman on that black box
冒着生命危险为正义而战的女人
risking her life to do the right thing.
你是我最好的朋友
My best friend...
在其他人都不支持的时候  是你
who supported me as a mother and a pilot
鼓励我成为一个母亲  一位飞行员
when no one else did.
你很聪明  很有趣  还是一个捣蛋鬼
You are smart, and funny, and a huge pain in the ass...
在你还不会用拳头喷火时
and you were the most powerful person I knew...
你就已经是我所知道的最强大的人了
way before you could shoot fire from your fists.
你听到我说的了吗
You hear me?
你  听到了吗
Do you hear me?
过来  过来  我的姐妹
Come here. Come here, girl.
没事了
I got you.
我知道我不值得你信任
I know I don't deserve your trust...
但你是我们唯一的线索
but you were our only lead.
我们发现你的能量特征
We discovered that your energy signature
与玛威尔的能量核心相匹配
matched Mar-Vell's core.
现在我们知道原因了
Now we know why.
要是你知道它对我的重要性就好了
If only you knew the importance of it to me.
我只是需要你的帮助
I just need your help
来解码  去玛威尔实验室的坐标
decoding the coordinates to Mar-Vell's lab.
那些不是坐标  它们是状态向量
Those weren't coordinates. They're state vectors.
关于轨道位置和速度的状态向量
For orbital position and velocity.
你在地球上找不到她的实验室
You didn't find her lab on Earth,
是因为它不在地球上
'cause it's not on Earth.
那是六年前那场撞击事件的发生地点
That was the location on the date of the crash six years ago.
如果我们跟踪它的路线
If we track its course,
就会在轨道上找到它
we'll find it in orbit right now.
这只是基本的物理常识
It's just basic physics.
在轨道上
In orbit?
这很难弄清楚吗
Was that so difficult to figure out?
我是说  你是我的科学家  对吧
I mean, you're my science guy, right?
勇·罗格很快会找上我的
Yon-Rogg will catch up to me soon.
我们必须在他之前找到能量核心
We've got to get to the core before he does.
我们要去太空吗
Mmm. We're going to space?
用什么去
In what?
对你的飞行器稍作调整应该就行
A few tweaks to your vessel should do it.
我可以做些改装
I can handle the modifications.
是你的科学家
Mmm. Your science guy.
我需要一个副驾驶
Well, I could use a copilot.
不  不  我不能
No. No, I can't.
我不能离开莫妮卡
I can't leave Monica.
妈妈  没关系的
Mom, it's okay.
我可以和外公外婆呆一起
I can stay with Gramma and Paw-paw.
我不会去的  宝贝  那太危险了
There's no way I'm going, baby. It's too dangerous.
测试全新的航空航天技术也危险
Testing brand-new aerospace tech is dangerous...
你以前不就是做那个的
and you used to do that.
你的计划是利用
Your plan is to leave the atmosphere
并非设计于此用的飞行器  飞出大气层
in a craft not designed for the journey...
而你预期遭遇的敌人
and you anticipate hostile encounters...
是具有极大技术优势的外敌
with a technologically-superior foreign enemy.
对吗
Correct?
这就是我要说的
That's what I'm saying.
-你必须去  -莫妮卡
- You have to go! - Monica!
你有机会
You have a chance
去执行历史上最酷的任务
to fly the coolest mission in the history of missions...
而你却要放弃它  然后坐在沙发上
and you're gonna give it up to sit on the couch
和我一起看《新鲜王子》吗
and watch Fresh Prince with me?
你说什么
What?
我只是觉得你应该想想
I just think you should consider...
你为你女儿树立了个什么样的榜样
what kind of example you're setting for your daughter.
这是怎么回事
What's going on around here?
我知道  我知道
I know, I know.
进去给你们解释  谢谢你们
I'll explain inside. Thank you.
你的妈妈很幸运
Your mom's lucky.
上苍恩赐孩子时
When they were handing out kids,
给了她最厉害的一个
they gave her the toughest one.
淘气包上尉
Lieutenant Trouble.
你记起来了
You remembered.
那是我的吗
Is that mine?
不  不
No, no.
我回来之前  你拿着
You hang on to it until I come back.
但是有件事我需要你的帮助
But there is something that I need your help with.
我再也不穿克里人的颜色了
I can't wear these Kree colors anymore.
而你显然是这里唯一一个
And since you are obviously the only person around here
有时尚敏锐度的人
with any sense of style...
所以呢
Hmm?
不行
No.
也不行
Uh-uh.
这个绝对不行
Definitely not.
我们现在可是队友了
Well, since we're on the same team...
我看起来怎么样
How do I look?
焕然一新
Fresh.
你怎么才来
What took you so long?
我挺好  谢谢关心
I'm fine. Thanks for asking.
-PRY46-B  -别对暗号了
- PRY46-B... - No, no codes.
我们都知道这个系统已经废了
That system is fallible, as we've learned.
行  那你问吧
Okay, then let's do this.
和至高智慧交流的时候  我看到的是谁
Who do I see when I commune with the Supreme Intelligence?
我猜是你最崇拜和尊敬的人
The person you most admire and respect, I'd guess.
但你从不告诉我是谁
But you would never tell me who.
那你对哈拉最早的记忆是什么
And what is your earliest memory of Hala?
输血
The transfusion.
我的血管里流着蓝血
Blue blood running through my veins.
谁的血
Whose blood?
她的血管里流着我的血
That's my blood that's coursing through her veins.
你对她做了什么
What have you done with her?
你来得太晚了
You're too late.
她知道了
She knows?
罗南  斯克鲁人已经渗透进C-53了
Ronan, Skrulls have infiltrated C-53.
立刻过来
Come at once.
为克里人而战  指挥官
For the good of all Kree, Commander...
我来歼灭这群祸害
the infestation will be eradicated.
飞行高度500  继续爬升
Passing 500 and climbing.
你最好别把那玩意儿抱在腿上
You know, you really shouldn't have that thing on your lap.
我们可算不上盟友
Our little alliance with you is tenuous at best.
只要他能继续把你吓得屁滚尿流
And as long as he continues to freak you out... like that...
我会一直全心全意的
yeah, I'm gonna keep giving him
爱着他  抱着他  宠着他
all the loves and hugs that he needs, right?
我能问你个问题吗
Can I ask you something?
你想变成什么都行吗
Do you just turn into anything you want?
我得先看一眼才能变
Ah, well, I have to see it first.
你们所有人都能变吗
Can you all do it?
从生理上来说  能
Physiologically? Yeah.
但这需要练习
But, uh, it takes practice...
而且要想变得像  说到底要拼天赋
and, um, dare I say it, talent to do it well.
-你能变成猫吗  -猫是什么
- Can you turn into a cat? - What's a cat?
能变成文件柜吗
What about a filing cabinet?
我为什么要变成文件柜
Why would I turn into a filing cabinet?
捕蝇草呢
A Venus flytrap?
如果你能变成捕蝇草
I'll give you 50 bucks right now
我马上给你50块钱
if you turn into a Venus flytrap.
引擎从超燃冲压模式切换到核聚变模式
Switching engines from Scramjet to Fusion.
大家系好安全带
Buckle up, folks.
这正常吗  像是气流扰动之类的吗
Is this normal, like, space turbulence?
差不多吧
Pretty much.
正在锁定坐标
Locking in on coordinate grid.
实验室在哪
Where is it?
是这里  就是这里
It's here. It's gotta be here.
它是在这片虚无的前面还是后面
Well, is it in front of all that nothing, or behind it?
隐形模式解除
Decloaking activated.
玛
威
尔
实
验
室
克
里
帝
国
巡
洋
舰
这就是能量核心
Is that it? The core?
她在笔记里把它叫做宇宙魔方
In her notes she called it the Tesseract.
喔
Whoa.
劳森怎么会有孩子的东西
What was Lawson doing with all this kid stuff?
这里还有别人
We're not alone.
塔洛斯
Talos!
他来这里不是为了宇宙魔方
He didn't come here for the Tesseract.
没事
It's okay.
我们不知道怎么办
We didn't know what to do.
玛威尔警告我们千万不要发出任何信号
Mar-Vell warned us not to send a signal for any reason...
否则克里人会发现我们
or the Kree would find us.
你做得对
You did the right thing.
没事  没事
It's okay, it's okay.
她是友军  她是朋友
She's all right. She's a friend.
我不会伤害你们的
I am not gonna hurt you.
是她带我找到你们的
She led me to you.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我之前都不知道
I didn't know.
卡罗尔
Carol.
这是战争
This is war.
我的双手也同样沾满了鲜血
My hands are filthy from it, too.
但是我们最终找到了族人
But we're here now.
是你带我们找到了我的族人
You found my family.
这只是个开始
This is just the beginning.
还有成千上万的族人
There are thousands of us separated from each other...
散落在整个星系中
scattered throughout the galaxy.
太空入侵者
要是我在一台弹球机上连着玩六年
If I played the same pinball machine for six years...
也能刷出高分来
I'd have some high scores, too.
和敌人好上了吗
Fraternizing with the enemy?
你怎么把战服弄成这样了
What did you do to your uniform?
我们猜对了  他们把她洗脑了
They got in her head. Just like we thought.
至高智慧会把她导回正轨的
The Supreme Intelligence will set her straight.
这些人都不是士兵
You can see they're not soldiers.
放他们走  你抓我吧
Let 'em go. You can have me.
能量核心呢
And the core?
你竟然骗我
You lied to me.
我是让你成为最好的自己
I made you the best version of yourself.
我们能赋予你超能力  也能夺走它
What's given can be taken away.
过来  快走  快点
Back here! Move, move!
给我过来  趴下
Get over here. Get down!
快走  快点  拿过来
Let's go! Go, move! Give me this！
你可来了
There she is.
看来待在C-53的日子唤醒了你的记忆
Seems like your time on C-53 jogged the old memory.
这件夹克
This jacket.
简直太帅了
It's killer, by the way.
哦
Oh.
这音乐  简直太搭了
The music. It's a nice touch.
放我出去
Let me out.
我做不到啊
No can do.
如果你敢伤害他们  我会把你烧成灰烬
If you hurt them, I will burn you to the ground.
用什么烧呢
With what exactly?
你的超能力是我们给你的
Your power comes from us.
我的超能力不是你们给我的
You didn't give me these powers.
是那场爆炸给我的
The blast did.
那又怎样  你太弱了
And yet, you've never had the strength
控制不了你的超能力
to control them on your own.
物种  噬元兽
Species: Flerken.
杀伤力  高
Threat: high.
它是只猫咪  不是汉尼拔
It's a cat, not Hannibal Lecter.
汉尼拔是虚构小说里的著名食人狂魔
物种：雄性人类
Species: human male.
威胁值：几乎为零
Threat: low to none.
那玩意儿明显坏了
That thing's clearly busted.
把噬元兽送上飞船
Load the Flerken onto the Helion.
其他人全都丢进太空
Eject the others into space.
你做得很好  王牌
You did good, Ace.
多亏了你
Thanks to you...
那些阴险的变形人
those insidious shapeshifters
再也不会威胁到我们的星球
will threaten our borders no more.
我曾经相信过你的谎言
I used to believe your lies...
但那些斯克鲁人只是渴望有个家园
but the Skrulls are just fighting for a home.
你说的是要去将他们灭族
You're talking about destroying them
仅仅因为他们不愿服从你的统治
because they won't submit to your rule.
而现在  我也不会服从
And neither will I.
我们找到了你  我们将你当作同胞
We found you. We embraced you as our own.
你夺走了我
You stole me.
远离我的家乡  我的家人  我的朋友
From my home, my family, my friends.
你这么拼命还真是可爱
It's cute how hard you try.
但是记住
But remember...
没有我们
without us...
放弃吧  卡罗尔
Give it up, Carol.
别站起来了
Stay down!
你很弱小
...you're weak.
你骑太快了  你得慢一点
You're going too fast! You need to go slow!
你有缺陷
You're flawed.
你这是想死吗
Are you trying to kill yourself?
无助
Helpless.
你太感性  太弱小了
You're too emotional and so weak.
你不属于这里
You don't belong out here!
我们救了你
We saved you.
控制好
Control it.
早就告诉你了  卡罗尔
I told you, Carol.
他们永远不会让你飞的
They'll never let you fly.
这可不是女孩子过家家
This ain't a game for little girls.
你的吻技就像马
You kiss like a horse.
你一周都撑不了  丹弗斯
You won't last a week, Danvers.
没有我们  你就只是个人类
Without us, you're only human.
你说得对
You're right.
我只是个人类
I'm only human.
在哈拉  你重生了
On Hala, you were reborn...
弗斯
Vers.
我的名字是卡罗尔
My name is Carol.
她在试着挣脱控制
She's trying to break out.
战斗中我一直将一手绑于身后
I've been fighting with one arm tied behind my back.
但是如果我不再受缚
But what happens when...
又会怎么样呢
I'm finally set free?
你知道你在发光  对吧
You know you're glowing, right?
我一会儿再解释
I'll explain it later.
带上宇宙魔方
Take the Tesseract.
把午餐盒留下
Leave the lunchbox.
-我吗  -是啊
- Me? - Yes.
我才不要碰那玩意儿
I'm not touching that thing.
你还要我给你找个烘焙手套吗
You want me to get you an oven mitt?
把斯克鲁人带上昆式战机然后快走
Get the Skrulls on the Quadjet and go.
带着噬元兽
Take the Flerken with you.
-那你呢  -我给你们争取一点时间
- What about you? - I'll buy you some time!
我现在要把你抱起来了
I'm picking you up now.
我这可是相信着你不会吃了我
I'm trusting you not to eat me.
你们好啊  大伙们
Oh, hey, guys.
要为宇宙魔方掰手腕吗
Arm wrestle for the Tesseract?
我曾经觉得你很有趣
I used to find you amusing.
把这事儿了结了吧
Let's put an end to this.
行吧
Okay.
好喵喵
Good kitty.
你一直都是明白的
You knew all along.
因为这个我们从来不出去玩吗
Is that why we never hung out?
不  因为我从来就不喜欢你
No, I just never liked you.
吃我一招
Incoming!
着急走吗
Hey, in a hurry?
别逼我这么做
Don't make me do this.
可以啊
Okay.
快点  大显身手
Come on, do your thing!
快点啊
Come on!
别这样
妈的  咕咕
Damn it, Goose.
你个墙头草
Pick a side.
把他们也带去飞机库
Take them to the hangar, too.
把他们都丢进太空
We'll blast them all into space.
大干一场
Play it cool.
就像哈瓦那那次
Just like Havana.
那东西在你这儿吗
Do you have the thing?
噬元喵把它吞了
Flerken kitty ate it.
快点  动起来
Come on, move!
快走
Move!
听我指令
Follow my lead.
遮住她的眼睛
Cover her eyes.
快上飞船
Onto the ship!
快走  快走
Let's go! Let's go!
声东击西玩得不错
Nice diversion.
我可以发誓我放进去的
I could have swore I put it in there.
米涅瓦  开运输舰把他们击落
Minn-Erva, take them down in the drop ship.
这就去
On it.
你还好吗  朋友
You all right, friend?
从没这么好过
Never better.
有个讨厌鬼紧追不放
We got a bogey coming in hot.
太好了  爽
Yes! Boom!
那他妈是个啥
What the hell was that?
部署弹道导弹
Deploy ballistic warheads.
这不可能
That's impossible.
C-53星球没有足够先进的防御系统
C-53 doesn't have a defense system
能够摧毁我们的导弹
advanced enough to destroy our warheads.
那不是他们的防御系统  罗南
That's not their defense system, Ronan.
击落她
Take her down.
回跳跃点
Return to the jump point.
下次再来取这武器
We'll be back for the weapon.
能量核心吗
The core?
这个女人
The woman.
我真为你感到骄傲
I'm so proud of you.
自从那天我在湖边发现你
You've come a long way
你已经走过了漫漫长路
since I found you that day by the lake.
但你是否能将自己的情绪
But can you keep your emotions in check
控制足够长的时间来与我一战
long enough to take me on?
还是说像以往一样  你会输给情绪
Or will they get the better of you as always?
我一直都告诉你
I always told you...
等到那一天
you'll be ready
你作为自己击败我  你就准备好了
the day you can knock me down as yourself.
我说的就是现在
This is that moment.
就是现在  弗斯
This is that moment, Vers!
收起你的能力
Turn off the light show...
来  证明给我看你能打败我  就算
and prove... prove to me you can beat me without...
我不需要向你证明什么
I have nothing to prove to you.
目的地  哈拉
Destination: Hala.
我不能空手回去
I can't go back empty-handed.
你不会空手回去的
You won't be empty-handed.
我要你帮我传递一个消息
I'm sending you with a message.
告诉至高智慧我很快就会了结它
Tell the Supreme Intelligence that I'm coming to end it.
这场战争  整个谎言  所有的一切
The war. The lies. All of it.
你不能这么做
You can't do this.
刚才真惊险呀  对不  咕咕
That was a close call, huh, Goose? Huh?
那些坏人还在那儿吗
Those bad guys still in there somewhere?
嗷
Ow!
我操
Mother Flerken!
你还好吗
You okay?
没事  就是被挠了一小下
Yeah. It's just a scratch.
糟了
No.
我不相信你最惊险的那场战斗
I can't believe you got in the raddest dogfight ever...
我竟然错过了
and I missed it.
要我说你来的刚刚好
I'd say you arrived just in time.
飞得很漂亮嘛你
Some nifty flying you did out there.
神盾局总需要一个像你一样优秀的飞行员
S.H.I.E.L.D. could always use a good pilot like you.
我会考虑的
I'll consider it...
前提是你别再说我飞的  漂亮
as long as you never call my flying "nifty" again.
你眼睛怎么样了
How's your eye?
每秒钟都在好转
Hmm. Getting better every second.
我就确认一下
Just so I'm clear...
你是索拉
you were Soh-Larr...
那个神盾局的特工吗
and the S.H.I.E.L.D. agent?
凯勒
Keller.
他把我老板绑架了  偷了他的身份
He tied my boss up, stole his identity.
我就借了一下他的长相  我又不是贼
I borrowed his likeness. I'm no thief.
这跟偷是有点像
It is a little like stealing.
你这会儿站哪边呢
Whose side are you on here?
你在康复之前都能呆在这
You're good to go here until you recover...
但你和你的家人得换一副新面孔
but you and your family are gonna need a new look.
我可以继续回去当你老板
I could go back to being your boss.
呃  别了
Uh, please don't.
别呀  我喜欢他那双漂亮的蓝眼睛
Come on. I loved sporting his beautiful blue eyes.
不要  你们的眼睛最好看了
No way. You guys have the best eyes.
一定别改变你的眼睛
Don't ever change your eyes.
她的眼睛很好看
She has beautiful eyes.
你真好
That's very sweet of you.
我尽量不那么慌张
I was trying not to panic...
我会帮你找到一个家
I'll help you find a home.
完成玛威尔未完成的
Finish what Mar-Vell started.
他们可以和我们住一起
They can stay here with us.
可以吗  妈妈
Can't they, Mom?
宝宝  他们在这不安全
They won't be safe here, baby.
卡罗尔阿姨说的对
Auntie Carol's right.
他们需要他们自己的家
They need their own home.
我很快就会回来的
I'll be back before you know it.
或者  我能飞上去在半路遇见你吗
Or maybe I could fly up and meet you halfway?
如果你像你卡罗尔阿姨一样
Ah, only if you learn to glow
会发光的话才可以哦
like your Auntie Carol.
或者我可以造一艘宇宙飞船
Or maybe I'll build a spaceship.
你又不知道
You don't know.
他确实不知道
He doesn't.
把宇宙魔方留在地球上
Keep the Tesseract on Earth.
藏起来
Hidden.
你确定这是迈威尔想要的吗
You sure that's what Marvel would want?
玛威尔
Mar-Vell.
我就是这么说的
That's what I said.
那是两个词  玛  威尔
It's two words. Mar. Vell.
玛威尔
Mar-Vell.
迈威尔听起来好多了
"Marvel" sounds a lot better.
就像迈威尔莱特
You know, like the Marvelettes.
Marvelettes: 奇异合唱团 美国黑人乐团
*噢  等一下邮差先生*
* Wait, oh yes, wait a minute Mister Postman *
*等等  邮差先生*
* Wait... Mister Postman. *
没想起来吗
Not ringing any bells?
接着唱  说不定我就想起来了
Keep singing. Maybe it'll come back to me.
我把它升级了
I upgraded it.
范围最少也能涵盖好几个星系
Range should be a couple galaxies, at least.
干嘛  你觉得我会给你打骚扰电话吗
What? You think I'm gonna crank call you?
只能紧急情况下使用  知道吗
For emergencies only, okay?
要是你啥时候路过这个星球的话
Well... if you're ever passing back through this galaxy...
记得一定要喊哥一声
be sure to give a brother a shout.
我把那个番茄酱洗掉了
We got the ketchup stain off.
谢谢  淘气包上尉
Thanks, Lieutenant Trouble.
说再见很困难  我也一样
It's hard for me to say goodbye, too.
去吧
Go on.
很高兴你回来了  局长
Glad to have you back, sir.
这个是给你的
This came for you.
所以  那是真的吗
So, is it true?
克里人因为你不肯交出宇宙魔方
That the Kree burned your eye out...
把你的眼睛烧坏了
because you refused to give them the Tesseract?
我不承认也不否认那个故事的真实性
I will neither confirm nor deny the facts of that story.
明白了
Understood.
我很遗憾的汇报
I'm sorry to report
我们还没找到宇宙魔方
that we still haven't found the Tesseract.
我相信它会出现在某个地方的
I'm sure it'll turn up somewhere.
当它出现之后我会让你知道的
I'll let you know when it does.
然后呢
Then what?
什么
Sir?
我们不知道
We have no idea
外太空还会有什么样的威胁
what other intergalactic threats are out there.
而我们那个单人安保部队
And our one-woman security force
在宇宙的另一边
had a prior commitment...
有更重要的任务
on the other side of the universe.
光靠神盾局也不能保护所有人
S.H.I.E.L.D. alone can't protect us.
我们得找更多
We need to find more.
更多武器吗
More weapons?
更多英雄
More heroes.
你觉得我们还能找到像她一样的人吗
You think you can find others like her?
我们起码找到她了  而且我们还没找过
Hmm, we found her, and we weren't even looking.
休息一下吧  局长
Get some rest, sir.
你还得做一个重大的决定
You got a big decision to make.
别走开 后面还有2个彩蛋
这简直是噩梦
This is a nightmare.
我经历过更糟的
I've had better nightmares.
不管那个东西刚在做什么
So, that thing just stopped
它停下来了
doing whatever the hell it was doing.
有什么消息吗
What do we got?
不管那个信号最终发到哪  它都会消失
Whatever signal it was sending finally crapped out.
我以为我们可以不用电池了
I thought we bypassed the battery.
是不用
We did.
电还插着  就是停下来了
It's still plugged in. It just stopped.
重启  继续发信号
Reboot it. Send the signal again.
我们甚至不知道这个是什么
We don't even know what this is.
弗瑞知道  就按他说的做吧  求你了
Fury did. Just do it, please.
一旦你收到了回信
You tell me the second you get a signal.
我要你告诉我谁在另一边
I wanna know who's on the other end of that thing.
弗瑞在哪
Where's Fury?